<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Michael Roberts Website</title>
    <link>http://michaelroberts.website/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Michael Roberts Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://michaelroberts.website/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a New Theme</title>
      <link>http://michaelroberts.website/post/creating-a-new-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://michaelroberts.website/post/creating-a-new-theme/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.
We&amp;rsquo;ll start with creating a new site with a very basic template.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrate to Hugo from Jekyll</title>
      <link>http://michaelroberts.website/post/migrate-from-jekyll/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://michaelroberts.website/post/migrate-from-jekyll/</guid>
      <description>Move static content to static Jekyll has a rule that any directory not starting with _ will be copied as-is to the _site output. Hugo keeps all static content under static. You should therefore move it all there. With Jekyll, something that looked like
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ images/ logo.png  should become
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ static/ ▾ images/ logo.png  Additionally, you&amp;rsquo;ll want any files that should reside at the root (such as CNAME) to be moved to static.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Competitions</title>
      <link>http://michaelroberts.website/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://michaelroberts.website/about/</guid>
      <description>Below is some of the competitions I&amp;rsquo;ve competed in and our placement:    Place Competition Location     1st Place &amp;nbsp; Department of Energy CyberForce Competition Chicago IL   2nd Place &amp;nbsp; National Collegiate Cyber Defense Competition - Co-Captain &amp;nbsp; Orlando,Fl   1st Place &amp;nbsp; UB Network Defense Lockdown competition - Captain &amp;nbsp; Buffalo, NY   1st Place&amp;nbsp; Information Security Talent Search - Captain &amp;nbsp; Rochester, NY   1st Place &amp;nbsp; eSentinel National competition - Captain &amp;nbsp; Online   1st Place &amp;nbsp; Leidos Cyber Challenge - Captain &amp;nbsp; Augusta, GA   Network Uptime Award &amp;nbsp; International Collegiate cyber defense Inviational &amp;nbsp; Seattle, WA   1st Place &amp;nbsp; Panoply Regional &amp;amp; National competition - Captain &amp;nbsp; Online   1st place &amp;nbsp; Southeast Collegiate Cyber Defense Competition - Co-Captain &amp;nbsp; Atlanta,GA   1st Student team &amp;nbsp; Symantec CTF - Captain &amp;nbsp; Online   National Finalist &amp;nbsp; CyberPatriot National Finals - Captain &amp;nbsp; Baltimore, MD    Speaking Engagements  Derbycon 8 Maintaining post-exploitation opsec in a world with EDR Florida &amp;ldquo;In Focus&amp;rdquo; Smart Homes and Security 2018 Technology Exchange Training the Next Generation of Information Security Professionals Fox 35 news - Good day Orlando - Security information for Black Friday 2017 Interviewed, mentioned, or pictured in 50+ print publications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(Hu)go Template Primer</title>
      <link>http://michaelroberts.website/post/goisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://michaelroberts.website/post/goisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>Hugo uses the excellent go html/template library for its template engine. It is an extremely lightweight engine that provides a very small amount of logic. In our experience that it is just the right amount of logic to be able to create a good static website. If you have used other template systems from different languages or frameworks you will find a lot of similarities in go templates.
This document is a brief primer on using go templates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with Hugo</title>
      <link>http://michaelroberts.website/post/hugoisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://michaelroberts.website/post/hugoisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>Step 1. Install Hugo Goto hugo releases and download the appropriate version for your os and architecture.
Save it somewhere specific as we will be using it in the next step.
More complete instructions are available at installing hugo
Step 2. Build the Docs Hugo has its own example site which happens to also be the documentation site you are reading right now.
Follow the following steps:
 Clone the hugo repository Go into the repo Run hugo in server mode and build the docs Open your browser to http://localhost:1313  Corresponding pseudo commands:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>